[opening theme song playing]
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Yo ♪
♪ Mmm-hmm, come on ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Uh ♪
♪ Ow! ♪
♪ Oh-ooh, yeah ♪
♪ Yo ♪
- ♪ Come on ♪
- ♪ Move the world, move, move ♪
♪ Now, look, if I step into the world
We can have some fun ♪
♪ Yo ♪
♪ Uh, move the world, move, move ♪
♪ Now, look, if I step into the world
Let you have some fun ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Mmm-hmm, right ♪
PEELING BACK THE LAYERS
[suspenseful violin music playing]
- And who might you be?
- I'm here from Horns Pharmaceuticals.
[squeaking]
[researcher] This way.
[clicking]
You must be Chief Deshico.
My name is Garmo,
from Horns Pharmaceuticals.
Pleasure.
Is this urgent?
In fact, it's a matter of life and death.
I assume you're aware of the incidents
involving young carnivores lately.
Yes.
Have a look at this.
The substances used in Kines
may be the culprit.
Oh?
[Louis] Myosin, actin, and myogen.
You see?
[Deshico] Those are meat proteins.
Indeed.
Imagine my surprise to find them
in an energy drink of all places.
However, there are only trace amounts,
not enough for consumption
to trigger a reaction.
Which suggests they may be reacting
with something carnivores naturally have,
affecting some kind
of neural functionality.
- I suppose you found something?
- Yes.
I found your research paper.
- Ah! You read that?
- Yes.
Though I couldn't immediately accept
your conclusions.
Mmm. [laughs]
Well, you don't say.
[snarls softly]
May I borrow that Kines?
Take it.
[whirring]
All right.
Now, this sample
is from a regular carnivore.
And you'll see, when I add in the Kines...
Mmm, no real change, is there?
Right.
Okay. Where is...
Ah! Here we are.
This next sample is from a carnivore
who routinely eats real meat.
When I add Kines to this...
[Louis gasps]
[Deshico] GST isozymes remain in the body
long after meat has been consumed.
If you have those GSTs,
they bind to the proteins in Kines
and become a fusion protein.
It's like eating a large amount of meat
without having to touch a spec of flesh.
So, if we can stop it
from binding together, then--
Mmm-mmm. No, no.
Why would we ruin a good thing?
[splutters] Because this is dangerous.
- We can't leave this out there.
- [grunts]
Here's the thing.
In our society, eating real meat
is strictly forbidden, right?
Right.
Okay, then. So, nobody is doing it,
are they?
Which means, it should be perfectly fine
to drink one of these.
- Theoretically, yes, but realistically--
- Oh, dear!
So you can't approve of Kines,
but you can ignore
illegal meat consumption?
Uh, no, that's--
Carnivores and herbivores coexisting
is simply twisted,
and Kines is an experimental drug
that'll bring this to light.
Doesn't that intrigue you?
No! Are you insane? This is wrong!
Yes. Very wrong, indeed.
A bit like impersonating
an industry colleague
to steal information.
- You do love to act, don't you, Louis?
- [huffs]
To think you went as far as to remove
your precious horns for the role.
I expect no less from a true thespian.
I know all about you.
You're the first and only herbivore
to ever run the Shishi-Gumi
after you killed their boss and took over.
- You're wrong.
- Ah, forgive me.
You're the ex-boss, aren't you?
- [huffs]
- Relax.
I have no intention of revealing
your sordid past to the world.
Then...
Their current boss is a character.
- Do you know him?
- Of him.
Do you know that Melon is a mix?
Melon?
- He's a gazelle and a carnivore?
- A leopard. Yes.
[gasps] I thought as much.
Incredible, right?
Mixes are the one subject
I'm most obsessed
with researching right now!
Of course, it's natural
for one to take interest
in the beasts they come into contact with
regardless of their sex or species.
But for me, those differences
make them even more alluring.
As a former Shishi-Gumi boss,
perhaps you can relate?
Why are you so drawn to mixed beasts
in particular?
Some mixes have extreme imbalances
in their senses or intuition or instincts.
It's really quite extraordinary
to see that in action.
- You're talking about super senses.
- Hmm.
They can perceive sounds or light
too faint to be measured
by scientific instruments,
or they might completely lack
appetite or sexual desire.
Do you think there's a connection
between senses and desires?
Well, at the moment,
that's just a hypothesis.
What I do know
is despite his slender build,
Melon possesses a ferocity
that rivals even the lions'.
Though I haven't collected any data
on his senses.
Do you have any information?
No, I've never had the pleasure
of meeting him.
I see. That's unfortunate.
[Louis] He's not wrong.
A lion should be able to overpower
that skinny creature easily.
But he exudes an intense authority.
Perhaps they were right
to be terrified of him.
Something about him is unsettling.
[cell phone vibrating]
CHLOE
This is Louis.
[Chloe] Hey. How'd it go?
I found out the cause at least.
Kines reacts with a substance that remains
in the body after meat consumption
and stimulates the nervous system.
I was afraid of that.
So, if someone has ever eaten meat,
there's a possibility
they could become violent.
We need to deal with this at once.
Don't tell me
you want to confront the supplier.
That's a tragedy waiting to happen.
No. Of course, you're right.
[huffs] I have another idea.
UDON BEBEBE
[Legoshi] I can't apologize enough.
I mean that. I'm so sorry.
Huh?
[Sunaga] Leftovers.
- Don't make me toss 'em.
- Huh?
Well, okay.
I appreciate it.
[Legoshi blowing, slurping]
[sighs]
Oh, that's good. I really needed this.
Not that I want to lecture you,
but in the future, I need you to call out
so I can make arrangements, okay?
You can't just skip out work
without saying anything to your boss.
I'm sorry, sir.
Now, what's all this about you
getting shot and killed by some big fruit?
- Melon? That's his name.
- Never mind the name.
You were shot and killed,
met up with your dead mother,
and then magically came back to life?
Who's going to believe that?
Everything I'm telling you is true.
[Sunaga sighs]
When you're finished, I need you to clean
the toilets and the exhaust vent.
Got it.
So warm. Makes me glad to be alive.
[Yahya] Were you able to find
any of that Melda he was talking about?
[Corne] Either it disappeared
or it was disappeared.
And now this mask
is the only lead we have left.
No attendee list to speak of,
Legoshi is missing,
and Melon's in the wind.
Well, have you considered the possibility
that the wolf may have tricked us?
Mmm, you think he's an accomplice.
He really was shot, you know.
I know. But was the gun meant
for large beasts?
[gasps, sighs]
- [elevator chimes]
- Hmm.
Mr. Yahya, is there any news on Melon?
To think my own wounds
have barely begun to heal,
and you're all bright-eyed
and bush-tailed.
- You really are something else, aren't ya?
- [chuckles]
Well, I am Gosha's grandson.
Oh! I'm so sorry. I'll come back.
No, you can stay.
Corne here has been my right hand
in the Melon investigation.
Look at that. Not every day
I meet a fellow scarface.
Good to meet you.
Uh, right back at ya. My name's Legoshi.
- [Yahya] Melon's gone, by the way.
- Hmm?
I'm sorry. I even had him
right in front of me.
It's fine.
It's entirely my fault for involving
an amateur like you in the first place.
I put you directly in harm's way.
Forgive me.
Uh, no. I wouldn't have gone
if I didn't want to.
That's not on you at all.
Gosha was worried sick about you.
Come on, you told my grandpa?
Yeah. He really chewed me out
for this one.
So you understand
why I can't involve you any further.
- But what if--
- This isn't up for discussion.
We're not discussing.
I'm telling you I'm not done here.
Listen, Melon can't get away.
I have to speak with him again.
If you know where he is,
please just tell me.
[inhales deeply] Hmm.
We don't have any leads right now.
Oh, I see.
Besides, there's no talking
to a guy like that.
Well, I can't know that unless I try.
Right? I'll do it alone.
[Legoshi grunts]
Hey!
[both] Hmm.
[theater owner] Number ten...
Number 11, number 12.
Good. Next is the cue light.
[theater owner gasps]
Hey! We're closed!
What are you doing in here?
Pardon me. Is there any chance Miss Cosmo
or Miss Luna are here right now?
[theater owner] What?
Uh, if you have business with those girls,
you'd better give up.
- They're not coming back.
- What?
PERFORMANCE CANCELED
So, um, regarding the person
who organized the party the other night--
Let it go. Get lost already.
I mean, any information would be helpful.
- Oh. Your tail...
- [gasps]
Mind your own business.
Quit bugging me, and get out of here!
- I don't want to cause you any trouble.
- Get it through your thick skull!
You're already causing me trouble,
you moron!
I lose my star performer,
my tail gets cut off...
[gasps]
[Yahya] And definitely don't mention
the investigation.
You'll put the ladies in danger.
[Legoshi] No.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I'll go now.
- Uh, but one more thing before I do--
- Piss off already!
The third light from the back,
it's burned out.
Huh?
[Legoshi] Sorry to have bothered you.
Oh, so it is.
Hey, wolf boy.
[Legoshi] Hmm?
Cosmo said she could see a strange pattern
through their shirt.
The host, I mean.
A strange pattern...
[Legoshi groans]
A pattern, huh?
I wonder... Hmm?
[snarls] What are you looking at?
[gasps, hums]
[exhales contentedly]
Ocean creatures, they don't know
how lovely this feels.
What a shame that is.
So you've decided you like the bath?
Yes, yes, I have at last.
That's good.
You were a little scared at first.
Indeed.
But once you showed me,
I've grown to like them.
Everyone is naked here.
Even land animals who wear so much clothes
to protect themselves.
In the bath, everyone is equal.
We're all shedding
the constraints of society.
Or something.
Together, yes.
And this way, we share our scars.
- Many scars.
- [hesitates]
Yeah, I...
- [Legoshi] I've been through a lot.
- [Sagwan] That is life.
Uh...
But eating good food and taking a bath,
you know, that's what makes me
feel like I'm living.
[gasps, hesitates]
Uh, please don't cry. Look, I'm all right.
These are not tears. It's bathwater.
Oh, uh...
In the sea, I've never cried before.
Many fish die there, but it's no big deal.
I don't cry, even when friends die.
Although, my good friend Legoshi,
if you were to die,
I would surely cry on land.
Oh, Mr. Sagwan...
I will teach you.
Listen.
If you are in trouble at sea,
just shout like this.
[inhales deeply]
[blubbering]
I, uh-- Wait a second. [inhales deeply]
[speaking in ocean language]
[gasps]
[in English] So, what does that mean?
What it means is,
"I am Legoshi, the Great Gray Wolf."
- Next, I'll teach you the magic words.
- [inhales deeply]
[speaking in ocean language]
[gasps]
[in English] Okay, what does that mean?
- That is secret.
- Uh, what?
Please tell me.
BATH HOUSE
Mr. Sagwan. Come on, please?
- What did you teach me how to say?
- Huh? [sniffs]
That smells nice.
[sniffs] Mmm, that does smell good.
Hey, don't change the subject.
[seller] Welcome.
OCTOPUS
Two orders, please.
- Capturing ocean creatures is a crime.
- [seller] Two? That'll be 600.
Mmm, I'll tell you what.
Since you're an ocean creature,
why don't I cut you a special deal
and make it 650 even?
That is very kind.
Hey, Mr. Sagwan.
What are you doing? This is wrong.
Oh, don't you worry. It's good.
- [seller] Thanks for your patience.
- Uh...
[Sagwan] Here is 600.
Ooh! That looks tasty!
- [sighs, gasps]
- [chomping]
No, wait, you have to stop.
You shouldn't be eating that.
It's a fellow sea creature, isn't it?
[gulps, exhales]
Legoshi, have you forgotten?
In the sea,
everyone must eat and is eaten.
It is just a fact of life.
Uh, yeah. Maybe.
- [hesitates] But don't you--
- [Sagwan] It is dead.
That is all. It cannot come back.
[chomping]
Mmm. [chuckles]
[Legoshi] He's not wrong.
It's just the food chain.
Logically, I get it.
But when I see it right in front of me, I...
[Sagwan sighs] That is delicious!
[Legoshi] Hmm.
Rather than an animal
who does not know the ways of the sea,
I will eat this friend.
That's better, right? What do you say?
Mmm, I guess.
Legoshi, you are kind. Very, very kind.
[Legoshi] Hmm.
But tasty things are tasty.
Just like udon is.
Well, udon isn't a living thing.
Thank you for the meal, young man.
Remember, poaching is illegal.
[chuckles nervously]
Mr. Sagwan, let's go. Come on.
Well, you had no problem eating it,
you jackass! [huffs]
[Melon] I think I'd like to give it a try,
if you don't mind?
[gasps]
- [Melon] I'll take one.
- [seller] Sure, that's 400.
[chews] Hmm.
[Melon] I was robbed of the taste buds
of both herbivore and carnivore.
No matter how much flavor I add,
no matter when or what I eat,
everything turns to ash in my mouth.
[spits]
I have no appetite, I have no libido,
I can't expose my face or body to anyone
without terrifying them.
There's only one place
I can truly reveal myself.
THE BLUE DRAGON
[male staff] Oh, Mr. Melon!
- Is that poky prick around?
- [laughs]
Yeah, he sent another customer
to the hospital today.
[male staff laughs]
I fired him,
but he'll be packing up for a while.
[Melon] What's up, Holger?
[slowly] Huh?
You know, it's almost adorable
they're trying to label you of all beasts
a psycho killer, isn't it?
You're just too stinkin' slow and stupid
to realize when your clients
are bleeding to death.
- [slowly] Huh.
- [gun cocks]
Come on, pal, you have to be polite
like everyone else.
- Put your heart in it.
- [slowly] Welcome in...
[Melon] That's better.
...my friend.
[Melon sighs wearily]
Can you believe this shit?
This leopard pattern
has finally spread down to my legs.
[sighs]
The same as usual.
Do your thing and fill in the foliage.
As many leaves as it takes to cover it.
[whirring]
NIMBLE
[grunts, sighs heavily]
[moaning]
That hits the spot!
[laughs]
I'll never get tired of this feeling.
[groaning] Right there!
- [whirring]
- [Melon laughs maniacally]
This pain is proof that I'm alive.
Oh, yeah!
The question is,
how long can I keep this up?
Or will I continue turning into a leopard?
[groaning]
[sniffs, sighs]
[sniffing]
Huh? [sniffs]
Excuse me.
Hmm. [sniffs]
[sniffing]
Hmm.
[sniffs]
Was I too late?
[gasps]
- [gasps]
- [laughs]
Sorry about that, buddy.
I didn't see you come in.
Oh, shit, don't worry,
nobody died in here.
The previous client
just bled a lot is all.
[Holger speaking slowly]
Be careful with that gun.
- Uh, gun?
- [laughs] Not you.
His slow ass is still
working on responding to the last guy.
Put it away,
Mr. Melon.
[Legoshi] He's talking to Melon.
[mysterious piano music playing]
Guess I should let him finish.
[music fades]
[closing theme song playing]
♪ Just like a new melody ♪
♪ Keep it beating on and on ♪
♪ I don't want to live without it ♪
♪ You give me the strength inside ♪
♪ Some things aren't meant to be ♪
♪ You say it like you know ♪
♪ But I really want you ♪
♪ I want you to see it the way I do ♪
♪ 'Cause every time I think about you ♪
♪ My heartbeat goes a-risin' ♪
- ♪ And I just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till I... ♪
♪ Till I die ♪
♪ There's nothing
That can beat like this ♪
♪ Faster as I close my eyes ♪
- ♪ Just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till the... ♪
♪ Till the night ♪
♪ Now as long as you are here by my side ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ I keep walking on ♪
♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪
- ♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
- ♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ I keep walking on ♪